https://globalstreams.com/legal-information/

Legal Information
I. Copyright Notice
This site contains copyrighted and proprietary information, including the design and layout of the GlobalStreams website, which is protected by United States copyright laws and international treaty provisions. This website may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part. No logo, graphic, sound or image from the GlobalStreams website may be copied or retransmitted unless expressly permitted by GlobalStreams.
II. Trademark Notice and Use
Notice
GLOBALSTREAMS, THE GLOBALSTREAMS LOGO, GLOBALSTREAMS CHROMA KEY TECHNOLOGY, GLOBECASTER, GLOBECASTER LIVE, GLOBECASTER POST, GLOBECASTER STUDIO, THE GLOBECASTER LOGO, GLOBECASTER SWITCHER, GLOBECASTER EDITOR, GLOBECASTER EFFECTS GENERATOR, GLOBECASTER CHARACTER GENERATOR, GLOBECASTER ANIMATOR/COMPOSITOR, GLOBECASTER ACE SEAT LICENSE, CONTENT INTEGRATION PLATFORM, CONTENT PROGRAM GUIDE, and “TV Production Studio In A Box” are trademarks of GlobalStreams.
TRINITY is a registered trademark of GlobalStreams. The names of other companies and products referenced on this site are trademarks of their respective owners.
This is not intended to be a complete list of GlobalStreams trademarks.
Usage
You may use GlobalStreams trademarks and service marks to refer to specific products of our company. Proper reference to our trademarks and service marks includes marking them with the appropriate trademark symbol. Additionally, when referencing a GlobalStreams mark, it must be used as an adjective, not as a noun or verb, followed by the proper generic name for the product.
It is requested that the following notice be provided on or within your product and/or product documentation which attributes ownership of a mark to GlobalStreams:
___________________ is a [registered, if applicable] trademark of GlobalStreams Corporation.
Privacy Policy
At GlobalStreams, we are committed to protecting your privacy. From time to time we may request certain information in order to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete privacy statement below.
Collection of Personal Information
On occasion we may ask you for certain information that personally identifies you. For example, this information may be requested if you are asked to respond to a survey, register before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, or when purchasing and registering GlobalStreams products. Any such personally identifiable information collected by GlobalStreams will generally be limited to name, e-mail address, country or location, but may include additional information when needed to provide a service you requested. There may, however, be a need for further information such as your shipping address, telephone number, etc.
Use of Personal Information
Your personal information may be usedfor various purposes, including:
Alerting you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from GlobalStreams.
Helping GlobalStreams create and deliver content and products most relevant to you.
Collecting GlobalStreams’ customer demographic data.
Improving overall GlobalStreams’ customer service.
We may hire other companies from time to time to provide services on GlobalStreams’ behalf, including the product registration, processing of surveys, packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, providing customer service, or sending direct mail literature. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they will be prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
GlobalStreams will disclose your personal information to third parties, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law; (b) act in urgent circumstances for personal safety reasons; (c) protect the rights or property of GlobalStreams; or (d) transfer the information in the event of a corporate transaction such as a merger or acquisition.
Security, Control and Correction of Personal Information
Except as otherwise stated herein, when your personal information is disclosed to GlobalStreams, GlobalStreams will not share that information with third parties without your permission. GlobalStreams strictly protects the security of your personal information and will carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
GlobalStreams may from time to time send out e-mails informing you of technical service or support issues related to a product or service you requested or purchased from GlobalStreams.
If at any time you feel your personal information is incorrect, please contact .
Modifications to this Statement
GlobalStreams reserves the right to modify or update this privacy statement without notice.
Questions or Comments? Any questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy should be directed to GlobalStreams email info@globalstreams.com
Stay Up to Date on News and Upgrades Whether one of the first or one of the newest in the GlobeCaster family, we will drop you a line from time to time.
Enter Email Address*
Products
GlobeCaster
GlobeCaster SystemsI/O’sFX Cards and ContentControl SurfacesGlobeCaster ACE Seat LicenseExtended Warranty Back
GlobeCaster Software DownloadsTechnical DocumentationFrequently Asked QuestionsForumsOnline TrainingLegacy Trinity and Snappy Support Back
About
ContactReturn Authorization PolicyLegal Information Back
